A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1991-1992
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files 1991-1992
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-2/1/2.941
This collection consists of 22,500 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred on 1998 February 9.
Scope and Content Information
These files constitute the major record series generated by John Thomas Casteen, the president of the University of Virginia. The records consist chiefly of correspondence, but also include reports, minutes, clippings, memoranda, and related papers concerning all areas of business of the president's office.
The papers consist of: general files, 1991-1992; seldom-used permanent files, 1972-1992; and committee files, 1987-1988.
Organization
SERIES I: General Files, 1991-1992 Boxes 1-40
SERIES II: Seldom Used Permanent Files, 1972-1992 Boxes 41-52
SERIES III: Committee Files, 1987-1988 Box 52
SERIES IV: Restricted Files Boxes 53-59
Contents List
- Series I: General Files
  - "A--Al" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 1)
  - "Am" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 1)
  - "An--Az" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Computing Services--General 1991-1992 (Box 1)
  - Admissions--General (2 folders) 1991-1992 (Box 1)
  - Admissions--Law 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - Admissions--Medical 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - African-American Affairs--General 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - African-American Affairs--Woodson Institute 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Association--General Board of Managers (5 folders) 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - American Association of State Colleges and Universities (empty) 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - American Council of Education--General (3 folders) 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - Annual Reports--President's Reports 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - Anthropology--General (Restricted) 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - Applications for Positions "A--Ho" 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - Applications for Positions "Hu-Z" 1991-1992 (Box 4)
  - Architecture--General 1991-1992 (Box 4)
  - Art--General 1991-1992 (Box 4)
  - Art--Bayly Museum 1991-1992 (Box 4)
  - Art--Planning and Development for the Arts 1991-1992 (Box 4)
  - Asian Studies--General (empty) 1991-1992 (Box 4)
  - Associated Chief Admissions Officers of Public Universities (empty) 1991-1992 (Box 4)
  - Associated Western Universities--General 1991-1992 (Box 4)
  - Association of American Colleges--General 1991-1992 (Box 4)
  - Association of American Universities (2 folders) 1991-1992 Jan-Jun (Box 4)
  - Association of American Universities (3 folders) 1991-1992 Jul-Dec (Box 5)
  - Association of Governing Boards--General 1991-1992 (Box 5)
  - Association of Virginia Colleges--General 1991-1992 (Box 5)
  - Astronomy--General (empty) 1991-1992 (Box 5)
  - Athletics--General (1 of 3) 1991-1992 (Box 5)
  - Athletics--General (2-3 of 3) 1991-1992 (Box 6)
  - Athletics--Atlantic Coast Conference 1991-1992 (Box 6)
  - Athletics--College Football Association 1991-1992 (Box 6)
  - Athletics--National Collegiate Athletic Association (3 folders) 1991-1992 (Box 6)
  - Athletics--Gator Bowl 1991-1992 (Box 6)
  - Athletics--Sugar Bowl/New Orleans 1991-1992 (Box 7)
  - Attorney General (State)--General 1991-1992 (Box 7)
  - Auditor--General 1991-1992 (Box 7)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts--General 1991-1992 (Box 7)
  - "Ba--Bem" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 7)
  - "Ben--Bm" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 7)
  - "Bn--Br" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 8)
  - "Bs--Bz" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 8)
  - Biology--General 1991-1992 (Box 8)
  - Birdwood--General 1991-1992 (Box 8)
  - Business and Finance--General 1991-1992 (Box 8)
  - Business and Finance--General Updates 1991-1992 (Box 8)
  - Business and Finance--Planning and Budget Committee (empty) 1991-1992 (Box 8)
  - Business Operations--General (empty) 1991-1992 (Box 8)
  - "Ca--Cam" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 8)
  - "Cam--Ce" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 8)
  - "Ce--Cg" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 9)
  - "Ch--Cn" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1991-1992 (Box 9)
  - "Co--Cz" Miscellaneous (1-2 of 5) 1991-1992 (Box 9)
  - "Co--Cz" Miscellaneous (3-5 of 5) 1991-1992 (Box 10)
  - Career Planning and Placement--General 1991-1992 (Box 10)
  - Casteen--General 1991-1992 (Box 10)
  - Center for Public Service--General 1991-1992 (Box 10)
  - Charlottesville, City of--General 1991-1992 (Box 11)
  - Charlottesville--Planning and Coordinating Council 1991-1992 (Box 11)
  - Chemistry--General 1991-1992 (Box 11)
  - Classics--General (Restricted) 1991-1992 (Box 11)
  - Clinch Valley College--General 1991-1992 (Box 11)
  - College of Arts and Sciences--General 1991-1992 (Box 11)
  - College Board--General (2 folders) 1991-1992 (Box 11)
  - Commerce--General (2 folders) 1991-1992 (Box 11)
  - Community Colleges--General 1991-1992 (Box 12)
  - Comptroller (State)--General 1991-1992 (Box 12)
  - Condolences "A--Z" 1991-1992 (Box 12)
  - Congress--General (2 folders) 1991-1992 (Box 12)
  - Consortia--General 1991-1992 (Box 12)
  - Capital (empty) 1991-1992 (Box 12)
  - Central Virginia (empty) 1991-1992 (Box 12)
  - Northern Virginia (empty) 1991-1992 (Box 12)
  - Tidewater 1991-1992 (Box 12)
  - Valley (empty) 1991-1992 (Box 12)
  - Western (empty) 1991-1992 (Box 12)
  - Continuing Education--General 1991-1992 (Box 12)
  - Council of Presidents--General 1991-1992 (Box 12)
  - Councils of Southern Universities--General (empty) 1991-1992 (Box 12)
  - "Da--De" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 13)
  - "Di--Do" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 13)
  - "Dr--Dz" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 13)
  - Darden School--General (2 folders) 1991-1992 (Box 13)
  - Dean's Meetings--General 1991-1992 (Box 14)
  - Development--General 1991-1992 Jan-Jun (Box 14)
  - Drama--General 1991-1992 Jul-Dec (Box 14)
  - "E" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 14)
  - Economics--General 1991-1992 (Box 14)
  - Education--General 1991-1992 (Box 14)
  - Educational Testing Service--General 1991-1992 (Box 14)
  - Engineering and Applied Science (2 folders) 1991-1992 (Box 15)
  - Engineering and Buildings--General (empty) 1991-1992 (Box 15)
  - English--General 1991-1992 (Box 15)
  - Enrollment--General 1991-1992 (Box 15)
  - Enrollment--Enrollment Statistics 1991-1992 (Box 15)
  - Environmental Sciences--General 1991-1992 (Box 15)
  - Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action 1991-1992 (Box 15)
  - "Fa--Fe" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 15)
  - "Fi" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1991-1992 (Box 16)
  - "Fl--Fz" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 16)
  - Faculty--General 1991-1992 (Box 16)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences--General 1991-1992 (Box 16)
  - Financial Aid to Students 1991-1992 (Box 16)
  - Food Services (Dining Services)--ARA 1991-1992 (Box 17)
  - French Language and Literature--General 1991-1992 (Box 17)
  - "Ga--Gn" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 17)
  - "Go--Gz" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 17)
  - General Assembly--General (2 folders) 1991-1992 (Box 17)
  - General Counsel--General 1991-1992 (Box 18)
  - General Services (State)--General 1991-1992 (Box 18)
  - German Languages and Literature--General (empty) 1991-1992 (Box 18)
  - Gifts and Grants "A--Ba" 1991-1992 (Box 18)
  - Gifts and Grants "Be--Cl" 1991-1992 (Box 18)
  - Gifts and Grants "Co--D" 1991-1992 (Box 18)
  - Gifts and Grants "E--G" 1991-1992 (Box 18)
  - Gifts and Grants "H--J" 1991-1992 (Box 19)
  - Gifts and Grants "K--M" 1991-1992 (Box 19)
  - Gifts and Grants "N--P" 1991-1992 (Box 19)
  - Gifts and Grants "Q--S" 1991-1992 (Box 19)
  - Gifts and Grants "T--Z" 1991-1992 (Box 20)
  - Governmental Relations--General 1991-1992 (Box 20)
  - Government and Foreign Affairs--General 1991-1992 (Box 20)
  - Governor--Administration 1991-1992 (Box 20)
  - Governor--Economic Development 1991-1992 (Box 20)
  - Governor--Education 1991-1992 (Box 20)
  - Governor--Finance 1991-1992 (Box 20)
  - Governor--General 1991-1992 (Box 20)
  - Governor--Health and Human Resources 1991-1992 (Box 20)
  - Governor--Natural Resources 1991-1992 (Box 20)
  - Public Safety 1991-1992 (Box 20)
  - Governor--Transportation (empty) 1991-1992 (Box 20)
  - Governor--Washington Liaison Office (empty) 1991-1992 (Box 20)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences--General 1991-1992 (Box 20)
  - "Hi--Hz" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 21)
  - Harrison Foundation--General 1991-1992 (Box 21)
  - History--General 1991-1992 (Box 21)
  - Honor System/Committee 1991-1992 (Box 21)
  - Housing--General 1991-1992 (Box 21)
  - Human Resources, Department of--General 1991-1992 (Box 22)
  - "I" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1991-1992 (Box 22)
  - Industrial Relations--General 1991-1992 (Box 22)
  - Information Technology(State)--General 1991-1992 (Box 22)
  - Information Technology and Communications 1991-1992 (Box 22)
  - Institutional Planning and Studies 1991-1992 (Box 22)
  - International Students--General 1991-1992 (Box 22)
  - International Studies--General 1991-1992 (Box 22)
  - "J" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 22)
  - Jefferson, Thomas Memorial Foundation--General 1991-1992 (Box 22)
  - Jefferson Scholars--General (Restricted) 1991-1992 (Box 22)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission (JLARC) 1991-1992 (Box 22)
  - Jefferson Restoration Advisory Board 1991-1992 (Box 23)
  - Jefferson Restoration Advisory Board Committee Newsletter (empty) 1991-1992 (Box 23)
  - "Ka--Ke" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 23)
  - "Kh--Kz" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 23)
  - "La--Le" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 23)
  - "Li--Lz" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 23)
  - Law School--General 1991-1992 (Box 24)
  - Lawn Use Policy (Restricted) 1991-1992 (Box 24)
  - Library--General 1991-1992 (Box 24)
  - "Mc" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 24)
  - "Ma--Me" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 24)
  - "Me--Mz" Miscellaneous (1 of 2 folders) 1991-1992 (Box 24)
  - "Me--Mz" Miscellaneous (2 of 2 folders) 1991-1992 (Box 25)
  - Marine Science--General 1991-1992 (Box 25)
  - Mariner's Museum--General 1991-1992 (Box 25)
  - Material Management--General 1991-1992 (Box 25)
  - Mathematics--General 1991-1992 (Box 25)
  - Medical Center--General (1-2 of 4 folders) 1991-1992 (Box 25)
  - Medical Center--General (3-4 of 4 folders) 1991-1992 (Box 26)
  - Medical Center--Personnel 1991-1992 (Box 26)
  - Medical Center--Health Sciences Council 1991-1992 (Box 26)
  - Medical Center--Hospital--General 1991-1992 (Box 26)
  - Medical Center--Hospital--Personnel 1991-1992 (Box 26)
  - Medical Center--Medical School--General 1991-1992 (Box 26)
  - Medical Center--Medical School--Personnel 1991-1992 (Box 26)
  - Medical Center--Nursing 1991-1992 (Box 26)
  - Medical Center--Nursing--Personnel--(empty) 1991-1992 (Box 26)
  - Music--General 1991-1992 (Box 26)
  - N--Na" Miscellaneous " 1991-1992 (Box 27)
  - "Na" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 27)
  - "Nb--Ne" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 27)
  - "Ni--No" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 27)
  - "No--Nz" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 27)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges--General 1991-1992 (Box 27)
  - (1-2 of 3)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges--General (3 of 3) 1991-1992 (Box 28)
  - Green Sheets 1991-1992 (Box 28)
  - Washington, D.C.--Executive Committee Meeting 1991 Nov 10-11 (Box 28)
  - Washington, D.C.--Marine Division Meeting 1991 Nov 10 (Box 28)
  - Washington, D.C.--Council of Presidents Meeting 1991 Nov 11 (Box 28)
  - Washington, D.C.--Marine Division Board Meeting 1991 Sep 16 (Box 28)
  - Marine Division (2 folders) 1991-1992 (Box 28)
  - National Science Foundation 1991-1992 (Box 28)
  - New England Education Loan Marketing Corporation (NELLIE MAE) (1 of 2) 1991-1992 (Box 28)
  - New England Education Loan Marketing Corporation (NELLIE MAE) (2 of 2) 1991-1992 (Box 29)
  - Newcomb Hall--General 1991-1992 (Box 29)
  - "O" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 29)
  - Oak Ridge Associated Universities 1991-1992 (Box 29)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa 1991-1992 (Box 29)
  - "Pa--Ph" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1991-1992 (Box 29)
  - "Pi--Piedmont" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 29)
  - "Pierce--Portugal" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 29)
  - "Post--Pz" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 29)
  - Parking--General 1991-1992 (Box 30)
  - Parking and Transportation--General (empty) 1991-1992 (Box 30)
  - Personnel--General 1991-1992 (Box 30)
  - Personnel--Training 1991-1992 (Box 30)
  - Philosophy--General 1991-1992 (Box 30)
  - Physical Plant--General 1991-1992 (Box 30)
  - Physical Plant--Project Status Reports (Construction Reports) 1991-1992 (Box 30)
  - Physics--General 1991-1992 (Box 30)
  - Planning and Budget (Capital Outlay) 1991-1992 (Box 30)
  - Planning and Budget (Medical) (empty) 1991-1992 (Box 30)
  - Planning and Budget (State) 1991-1992 (Box 30)
  - Planning and Budget (University of Virginia)--General 1991-1992 (Box 30)
  - President's Senior Cabinet Meetings 1991-1992 (Box 30)
  - Promotions--General 1991-1992 (Box 30)
  - Provost--General 1991-1992 (Box 31)
  - Provost--Associate Provost for Research 1991-1992 (Box 31)
  - Psychology--General 1991-1992 (Box 31)
  - "Q" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 31)
  - "Ra--Rh" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 31)
  - "Ri--Rz" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 31)
  - Real Estate Foundation--General 1991-1992 (Box 31)
  - Real Estate and Risk Management (empty) 1991-1992 (Box 31)
  - Recommendations "A--L" 1991-1992 (Box 31)
  - Recommendations "M--Z" 1991-1992 (Box 32)
  - Registrar 1991-1992 (Box 32)
  - Religious Studies--General 1991-1992 (Box 32)
  - ROTC--General 1991-1992 (Box 32)
  - ROTC--Air Force 1991-1992 (Box 32)
  - ROTC--Army 1991-1992 (Box 32)
  - ROTC--Navy 1991-1992 (Box 32)
  - "Sa" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 32)
  - "Sc--Sh" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 32)
  - "Si--Sn" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 33)
  - "So" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1991-1992 (Box 33)
  - "Sp--Sta" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 33)
  - "Stu--Sz" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 33)
  - Salaries--General 1991-1992 (Box 33)
  - Senate (University) (3 folders) 1991-1992 (Box 34)
  - Slavic Languages and Literatures (empty) 1991-1992 (Box 34)
  - Sociology--General 1991-1992 (Box 34)
  - South Africa--General 1991-1992 (Box 34)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools 1991-1992 (Box 34)
  - Southern Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities (empty) 1991-1992 (Box 34)
  - Southern Regional Education Board 1991-1992 (Box 34)
  - Space and Energy Management (empty) 1991-1992 (Box 34)
  - Spanish, Italian and Portuguese--General 1991-1992 (Box 34)
  - Sponsored Programs--General (empty) 1991-1992 (Box 34)
  - State Council of Higher Education 1991-1992 Jan-Jun (Box 35)
  - State Council of Higher Education of Virginia (SCHEV) (2 folders) 1991-1992 Jul-Dec (Box 35)
  - State Council of Higher Education of Virginia (SCHEV)--Assessment 1991-1992 (Box 35)
  - State Council of Higher Education of Virginia (SCHEV)--Commission on the Universities of the 21st Century 1991-1992 (Box 35)
  - State Council of Higher Education of Virginia (SCHEV)--Council Notes 1991-1992 (Box 35)
  - State Council of Higher Education of Virginia (SCHEV)--On Line (empty) 1991-1992 (Box 35)
  - State Council of Higher Education of Virginia (SCHEV)--Research Note 1991-1992 (Box 35)
  - State Department of Education--General 1991-1992 (Box 35)
  - State Fire Marshal (empty) 1991-1992 (Box 35)
  - State Council of Higher Education of Virginia 1991-1992 (Box 35)
  - Student Affairs--General (Restricted) 1991-1992 (Box 35)
  - Student Affairs--General (Restricted) 1991-1992 Jul-Dec (Box 35)
  - Student Affairs--Fraternities/Sororities--General (Restricted) 1991-1992 (Box 36)
  - Student Council--General (Restricted) 1991-1992 (Box 36)
  - Student Council--Minutes (Restricted) 1991-1992 (Box 36)
  - Summer Session--General 1991-1992 (Box 36)
  - "Ta--Te" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 36)
  - "Tf--Tz" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 36)
  - Treasurer--(State)--General 1991-1992 (Box 36)
  - Travel Invoices 1991-1992 (Box 36)
  - Travel Vouchers--John Casteen 1991 Jul-Dec (Box 36)
  - Travel Vouchers--John Casteen 1992 Jan-Dec (Box 36)
  - "U" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1991-1992 (Box 37)
  - United States Savings Bonds 1991-1992 (Box 37)
  - United Way/Combined Charities Campaign 1991-1992 (Box 37)
  - Universities Research Association 1991-1992 (Box 37)
  - University Guides 1991-1992 (Box 37)
  - University Journal (Restricted) 1991-1992 (Box 37)
  - University Police 1991-1992 (Box 37)
  - University Press of Virginia 1991-1992 (Box 37)
  - University Relations/News Office (2 folders) 1991-1992 (Box 38)
  - University Union 1991-1992 (Box 38)
  - "V--VaAl" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 38)
  - "Va.As--Va.Co" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 38)
  - "Va.Co--Va.Cu" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 38)
  - "Va.De--Va.Mu" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 38)
  - "Va.T--Vz" Miscellaneous (3 folders) 1991-1992 (Box 39)
  - Virginia Academy of Science 1991-1992 (Box 39)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review 1991-1992 (Box 39)
  - Virginia Student Aid Foundation (VSAF) 1991-1992 (Box 39)
  - Virginia Festival of American Film (3 folders) 1991-1992 (Box 39)
  - "W--Wa" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 40)
  - "Wa--We" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 40)
  - "We--Wh" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 40)
  - "Wi--Wo" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 40)
  - "Wo--Wom" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 40)
  - "Wo--Wz" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 40)
  - "X,Y,Z" Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 40)
- Series II: Seldom-Used Permanent Files
  - Worrell, Thomas E., Junior 1984-1992 (Box 41)
  - Darden, Joshua P., Junior (4 folders) 1982-1986 (Box 41)
  - Admissions--Law (Restricted) 1991-1992 (Box 41)
  - Admissions--Medicine (Restricted) 1991-1992 (Box 41)
  - Admissions--Architecture (Restricted) 1991-1992 (Box 41)
  - Admissions--Darden School (Restricted) 1991-1992 (Box 41)
  - Graduate Arts and Sciences--Admissions (Restricted) 1992 Fall (Box 41)
  - Admissions (4 folders) (Restricted) 1991-1992 (Box 41)
  - Task Force--Drug Abuse/Education 1987 (Box 41)
  - Task Force--Alcohol/Drug Abuse/Education (5 folders) (Restricted) 1987 (Box 41)
  - Report of Task Force on Drug and Alcohol Abuse 1987 (Box 41)
  - AAU Membership List 1991-1992 (Box 42)
  - Association of American Universities Membership List 1990-1987 (Box 42)
  - Association of American Universities Membership List 1986-1983 (Box 42)
  - Association of American Universities Membership List 1974-1982 (Box 42)
  - Buckley Amendment 1976-1987 (Box 42)
  - Cambridge Associates 1981-1986 (Box 43)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--General (3 folders) 1986-1991 (Box 43)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--Advisory Board (1 of 2) 1986-1991 (Box 43)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--Advisory Board (2 of 2) 1986-1991 (Box 44)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--Memberships 1986-1991 (Box 44)
  - Development--Corporate Alumni List 1986 (Box 44)
  - Development--Development Council 1986-1989 (Box 44)
  - Development--Proposals Pending 1986 (Box 44)
  - Development--Forbes 400 1985 (Box 44)
  - Development--Law School 1985 (Box 44)
  - Development--Permanent (3 folders) 1976-1991 (Box 45)
  - Development--Provost 1976-1991 (Box 45)
  - Endowment Fund--General (1 of 2) 1976-1989 (Box 45)
  - Endowment Fund--General (2 of 2) 1976-1989 (Box 46)
  - Endowment Fund--President's Contingent (3 folders) 1986-1991 (Box 46)
  - Hunt, Ray C. Junior 1984-1992 (Box 47)
  - Institute of Government Advisory Board 1981--1982 (Box 47)
  - Handicapped (Restricted) 1979-1991 (Box 47)
  - Lawn Society--October 1991 Meeting 1991 Oct (Box 47)
  - Lawn Society--October 1990 Meeting 1990 Oct (Box 47)
  - Medical Center--Institute for Substance Abuse Studies (4 folders) 1987-1992 (Box 47)
  - Miller Center--General (4 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 48)
  - School of Architecture--Bienniel Evaluation and Planning Report 1984-1990 (Box 48)
  - Vice President's Bienniel and Planning Summary Reports 1984 Dec (Box 48)
  - Planning and Budget--University (permanent) 1984-1990 (Box 49)
  - Sociology--Patricia A. Taylor 1989-1991 (Box 49)
  - University Policy (2 folders) 1961-1979 (Box 49)
  - Visitors--General (1 of 5) 1991-1992 (Box 49)
  - Visitors--General (2-5 of 5) 1991-1992 (Box 50)
  - Task Force to Evaluate Alcohol and Other Drug Policies... 1991 (Box 50)
  - Planning and Budget--Medical Center--Report 1984-1990 (Box 51)
  - Planning and Budget--Medical Center--Appendices 1984-1990 (Box 51)
  - Task Force: Discrimination Complaint Procedures (1-3 of 4) 1972-1988 (Box 51)
  - Task Force: Discrimination Complaint Procedures (4 of 4) 1972-1988 (Box 52)
  - Task Force--Drug/Alcohol Abuse and Education (2 folders) 1987-1990 (Box 52)
- Series III: Committees
  - Ad Hoc Committee--Early Retirement Incentives 1987 (Box 52)
  - Ad Hoc Committee--Search for Dean of African-American Affairs (Restricted) 1988 (Box 52)
  - Ad Hoc Committee--Search for Associate Provost for Academic Student Support (Restricted) 1988 (Box 52)
  - Ad Hoc Committee--International Studies Dean Search (Restricted) 1987-1988 (Box 52)
  - Ad Hoc Committee--Search for Dean of International Studies Program (3 folders) (Restricted) 1986-1988 (Box 52)
- Series IV: Restricted materials
  - General Files, A--H (Box 53)
  - General Files, I--R (Box 54)
  - General Files, S--Z (Box 55)
  - Permanent Files, from Box 41 (Box 56-57)
  - Permanent Files, C--E, H, L, V; Committee Files, from Box 52 (Box 58)
  - Committee Files, from Box 52 (Box 59)